Introduction
Chapter 1 How Brands Became More Important Than Products
Chapter 2 The Hidden World of Outsourcing and Labor
Chapter 3 The Illusion of Choice and the Power of Marketing
Chapter 4 The Privatization of Public Space and Culture
Chapter 5 The Rise of Resistance and Culture Jamming
Chapter 6 The Brand Expands—Colonizing Childhood and Identity
Chapter 7 The Global Factory—Lives Behind the Label
Chapter 8 The New Face of Activism—Networks, Boycotts, and Hope
Chapter 9 Searching for Alternatives—Ethical Consumption and Beyond
Chapter 10 Reclaiming the Future—Imagination, Community, and Change
Conclusion